http://www.bop.gov/website/privacy_policy.jsp

Resources
Find a document ...
Records Available Online
Resources For ...
Privacy Policy
The BOP privacy policy described below conforms to the Department of Justice's Privacy Policy
Information We Collect
If you access information on our website, the following basic information is automatically collected and stored on
our servers:
The name of the internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account,
or "yourschool.edu" if you are connecting from a university's domain)
The Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet)
from which you access our site
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site
The date and time you access our site
The internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site
The pages you visit and the information you request
The Federal Bureau of Prisons does not use this information to track the browsing of individuals who access the site. This information is
primarily collected for statistical analysis and technical improvements to the site. This government computer system uses software programs
to create summary statistics, which may be used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining
technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. In certain circumstances, however, we may take additional
steps to identify you based on this information and we may share this information, including your identity, with other government agencies.
[Back to top]
How We Use Your Personal Information
You do not have to provide any personal information to visit this website. If you choose to provide us with personal information, such as by
sending a message to an e-mail address on this website or by filling out a form and submitting it through our website, we will use that information
to respond to your message or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. If you submit your résumé to us electronically, we will use your
personal information to consider your application for employment.
The Bureau of Prisons does not collect or use information for commercial marketing.
We may share information you give us with contractors acting on our behalf or with another government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency.
In other limited circumstances, such as responses to requests from Congress and private individuals, we may be required by law to disclose information
you submit. If you provide comments in response to a request for public comments, we may make those comments, as well as your identity, available to
the public in a publication or by posting them on our website.
Where possible, we may give you more specific guidance at the point of collection
regarding how your personal information may be used or disclosed.
Electronically-submitted information is maintained and destroyed according to the principles of the Federal Records Act and the regulations and
records schedules of the National Archives and Records Administration, and in some cases, may be covered by the Privacy Act and subject to the
Freedom of Information Act (FOIA). A discussion of the FOIA can be found at:
http://www.justice.gov/oip/foia_guide09.htm and a discussion about the
Privacy Act can be found at http://www.justice.gov/opcl/privacyact1974.htm.
Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is sensitive or includes personal information, you may
prefer to send it by postal mail instead.
[Back to top]
Children
We believe in the importance of protecting the privacy of children online and do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children
under 13.
Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13.
[Back to top]
Cookies
Website measurement and customization technologies (commonly called "cookies") are small bits of text that are downloaded to your internet browser
when you visit a website. The Office of Management and Budget Memorandum
M-10-22, Guidance for Online Use of Web Measurement and Customization Technologies
defines conditions under which Federal agencies may use session and persistent cookies, and categorizes
them in "tiers" to identify their characteristics.
Session cookies
Session cookies are not stored on your computer's hard drive, and are removed when you complete your session or exit the site. Some Department
websites use these "Tier 1" session cookies to provide streamlined navigation and statistical analysis. No personally identifying information
is gathered.
Persistent cookies
"Tier 2" persistent cookies remain on your computer's hard drive after you complete an activity.
Google Analytics Premium
uses persistent cookies to measure how new and returning visitors use our websites over time. These persistent cookies do not collect any
personally identifying information, and the information that is collected is only used to improve our website.
To prevent your data from being
collected, you can download and install the
Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on created by Google.
(See related: Google’s main privacy policy)
You may control permissions for cookies on this or any other website by adjusting your individual
browser settings for customized privacy protection - see
http://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions.shtml
for helpful guidance. You can
still use Department websites if you do not accept the cookies, but you may be unable to use certain cookie-dependent features.
[Back to top]
External Sites
The Department's websites may contain links to websites created and maintained by other public and/or private organizations.
We provide
these links as a service to visitors to our site.
When you follow a link to an external site, you are leaving the Federal Bureau of Prisons'
website and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the external site.
[Back to top]
Security
For site security purposes and to ensure this service remains available to all users, this Government computer system employs software programs
to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Anyone using this system
expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that, if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence
may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on this server are strictly prohibited
and may be punishable by law, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act of 1996.
[Back to top]
Resources For ...
UNICOR.
FACEBOOK
TWITTER
LINKEDIN
USAJOBS
